(Sheldon:)I'd love to have you
join us on a double date.
(Amy:)Aw...
(Amy:)You are aware that a double date
doesn't count as two dates.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, then come
or don't.
(Sheldon:)I don't care.
(Bernadette:)I can't believe you're sore.
(Howard:)Hey, even professional pitchers
need a rubdown after the game.
(Bernadette:)But they throw
an actual ball.
(Bernadette:)You were throwing
air at a TV.
(Howard:)For your information,
(Howard:)I also gave Leonard
one hell of a high five.
(Bernadette:)I'm kind of surprised
you agreed to do this
(Bernadette:)in front of a stadium
full of people.
(Howard:)They're doing Space Day
and NASA asked me.
(Howard:)I felt like I couldn't say no.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Bernadette:)Well, if you want,
I could help you practice.
(Bernadette:)I played a lot of softball
growing up.
(Howard:)Thank you, that
would be great.
(Howard:)Great.
And while we're at it,
(Bernadette:)maybe we could butch up your run
(Bernadette:)for when you head out
to the mound.
(Howard:)What's wrong with the way I run?
Oh, just kidding.